JACK GILBERT

Multimedia Designer

(952) 215-5879 🖀

https://designergilby.github.io/portfolio/

PROFILE

A designer that's proven to be an incredibly quick learner with an excellent work ethic. Experienced in multiple facets of design, programming and technical troubleshooting while demonstrating strong leadership. Work experience includes advertising design, video game technologies, and web design/development. Also an active member of the LGBT+ community.

EDUCATION

May 2023

UNIVERSITY OF WISCONSIN - STOUT B.F.A. in Graphic Design, focus in Interactive Media Minor in Computer Sciences

June 2018

EDINA SENIOR HIGH SCHOOL High School Diploma

SKILLS

- Adobe Suite
- Figma
- Graphic Design
- Web Design
- Illustration
- Programming
- UX/UI Design
- Video Technologies
- **Event Technologies**
- Video Game Technologies

EXPERIENCE

June 2023 - Present

Junior Designer SIXSPEED

Tasked with conceptualizing designs for client facing projects and leading in-house creative projects. Grew from an internship position to a junior postion.

September 2022 - May 2023

Student Designer **UNIVERSITY OF WISCONSIN - STOUT**

Demonstrated skills in graphic design, web design and motion design with a focus in client-based work. Worked collaboratively with a small team of designers.

January 2020 - May 2023

Video Technician

UNIVERSITY OF WISCONSIN - STOUT

Demonstrated skills in event technologies with a focus in video. Lead small teams for set up and tear down of complex events. Promoted in April of 2022.

June 2022 - August 2022

Design Intern

FEDERAL RESERVE BANK OF MINNEAPOLIS

Demonstrated skills in graphic, motion, logo and signage design. Displayed ability to present work to clients and collaborate in a small team.

January 2021 - January 2022

Web Developer

UNIVERSITY OF WISCONSIN - STOUT

Managed the UW-Stout student events webpage. Tasked with maintaining updates and creating microsites for larger events.